<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on M3TFluiDLab</title>
    <link>https://github.com/ItisAriya/M3TFluiD_Lab/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on M3TFluiDLab</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/ItisAriya/M3TFluiD_Lab/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post 3</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ItisAriya/M3TFluiD_Lab/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://github.com/ItisAriya/M3TFluiD_Lab/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum. Deserunt esse cillum Lorem non magna adipisicing mollit amet consequat.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 2</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ItisAriya/M3TFluiD_Lab/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://github.com/ItisAriya/M3TFluiD_Lab/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia. Velit id fugiat occaecat do tempor. Sit officia Lorem aliquip eu deserunt consectetur. Aute proident deserunt in nulla aliquip dolore ipsum Lorem ut cupidatat consectetur sit sint laborum. Esse cupidatat sit sint sunt tempor exercitation deserunt. Labore dolor duis laborum est do nisi ut veniam dolor et nostrud nostrud.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pub</title>
      <link>https://github.com/ItisAriya/M3TFluiD_Lab/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://github.com/ItisAriya/M3TFluiD_Lab/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;publications&#34;&gt;Publications&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sharma, S.N. and Goudarzi, N.&lt;/strong&gt;, 2023, August. Urban airflow analysis using reduced-order modeling. In ASME Power Conference (Vol. 87172, p. V001T05A001). American Society of Mechanical Engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mortazavian, J., Sharma, S. and Goudarzi, N.&lt;/strong&gt;, 2024. Urban Wind Energy Assessment Near High-Rise Buildings within Different Urban Morphology: Insights from CFD and POD. In ASTFE Digital Library. Begel House Inc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mortazavian, J. and Goudarzi, N.&lt;/strong&gt;, 2024, July. Techno-Economic Assessment of Urban Wind Energy Near Various Common Building Configurations. In Fluids Engineering Division Summer Meeting (Vol. 88131, p. V002T05A029). American Society of Mechanical Engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mortazavian, J. and Goudarzi, N.&lt;/strong&gt;, 2024, September. Multi-Fidelity Machine Learning Analysis of Wind Patterns Around High-Rise Buildings. In ASME Power Conference (Vol. 88186, p. V001T06A008). American Society of Mechanical Engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Najian, M., &amp;amp; Goudarzi, N.&lt;/strong&gt; CFD Analysis for a Wind Tunnel Experiment for Investigating the Performance of Turbulence Models. In ASCE Inspire 2023 (pp. 895-904).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Najian, M., Sharma, S., &amp;amp; Goudarzi, N.&lt;/strong&gt; (2024, September). Effect of Non-Isothermal Conditions on Wind Patterns Near Isolated High-Rise Buildings. In ASME Power Conference (Vol. 88186, p. V001T06A009). American Society of Mechanical Engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sharma, S., Najian, M., &amp;amp; Goudarzi, N.&lt;/strong&gt; (2024, July). Towards Improving High Spatiotemporal Weather Forecast Accuracy With Data-Driven Modeling. In Energy Sustainability (Vol. 87899, p. V001T01A012). American Society of Mechanical Engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Najian, M., &amp;amp; Goudarzi, N.&lt;/strong&gt; (2023, August). Evaluating critical weather parameters using machine learning models. In ASME Power Conference (Vol. 87172, p. V001T04A006). American Society of Mechanical Engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Najian, M., &amp;amp; Goudarzi, N.&lt;/strong&gt; (2024, July). Sustainable Building Energy Modeling: the Synergistic Interplay of Urban Heat Island, Heat Waves, and Climate Zones. In Fluids Engineering Division Summer Meeting (Vol. 88124, p. V001T01A027). American Society of Mechanical Engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
